uvdesk.com 2019-04-03

# Privacy Policy - UVdesk Helpdesk

Thank you for visiting [www.uvdesk.com](http://uvdesk.com/) (together with its content, subdomains, software available for download, tools and services, the (“Site”), which is operated by Webkul Software Private Limited . Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this Site.

## INTRODUCTION

This is the privacy and cookies policy for UVDESK.com and our associated services both online and offline as well as through email communications that we send to you (together, the Site). The Site is operated by Webkul Software Pvt Limited (we, us and our). “You” or a “user” refers to any individual who visits or otherwise uses the Site, you are accepting and agreeing to the practices outlined in this privacy and cookies policy.

We are committed to protecting your privacy online. We appreciate that you do not want the personal information you provide to us distributed indiscriminately and here we explain how we collect information, what we do with it and what controls you have. By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of information in accordance with this privacy policy.

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy from time to time by changing it on the Site.

## CONSENT AND MODIFICATION

By using this Site, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy and to Webkul Software Private Limited processing of Personal Information for the purposes set forth herein. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change this Privacy Policy at any time, which change will be effective 30 days following posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Site. Your continued use of our Site 30 days following such posting means you will accept those changes.

## INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU

We may collect and process the following information about you:

  * Information (such as your name, title, company name, email address, job function or position, social media details, postal address and telephone number)

  * IP Address provided by your Internet Service Provider (ISP)

  * your log-in and password details

  * any transactions made by you through the Site like billing address

  * communications you send to us, for example, to report a problem or to submit queries, concerns or comments regarding the Site or its content; and

  * information from surveys that we may, from time to time, run on the Site for research purposes, if you choose to respond to, or participate in, them.

  * Information that helps us in identifying the products and services that best meet your requirements

  * Feedback from you about our website and our products and services generally.

  * You are under no obligation to provide any such information. However, if you should choose to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you with certain services.

## NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

Additional information that is collected might include, for instance, browser and device information; App usage data; information collected through cookies, pixel tags, and other technologies; demographic information and other information provided by you; or aggregated information. We use this information to facilitate our operation of the Sites and for other purposes described below.

## RECEIPT AND COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

We receive and/or collect information from you in the following ways:

  * ### General Access to the Site

We do not currently require you to provide Personal Information in order to have access to general information available on our Site.

  * ### Content Downloads

We offer you the opportunity to download certain content( archive files , video, image, data, text, documents, or other content ) from the Site without charge. If you choose to do so, you may first be required to provide certain Personal Information (for example, by completing an online purchasing and pricing form), such as your name, email address, phone number, job title, company name, country, industry, total annual revenue, and number of employees.

  * ### Purchases

If you choose to purchase a service or product from us we will require sufficient information from you to complete the transaction. Such information could include a credit card number and related account and billing information, invoice related information, and other data required to process the order. We may also update such data should you grant us permission to bill you or your credit card for recurring charges, such as monthly or other types of periodic payments. We may use the tools, software or services of third-party service providers to process transactions on our behalf (but we require that these parties agree to comply with this Privacy Policy). All information of this nature is maintained by us in a secure database and transmitted across the Internet from you to us using secured transmission encryption. Except as set forth herein, we will not share your financial Personal Information with any third person or entity.

We may provide you, via the Site, with the opportunity to contact us, receive a Webkul Software Private Limited newsletter or participate in conferences, webinars, or special promotional or other programs (collectively “Events”). In order to participate in any of these Events, you will be required to provide certain Personal Information which may include your name, company, job title, address, email address, and phone number.

  * ### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Some of our Site pages utilize “cookies” and other tracking technologies. A “cookie” is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Site user. You may block cookies, or delete existing cookies, by adjusting the appropriate setting on your browser. Please consult the HELP menu of your browser to learn how to do this. If you block or delete “cookies” you may find the usefulness of our Site to be impaired.

  * ### Log Files

Like many other websites, this Site may make use of log files. The information inside the log files includes the IP address from which you access the Site, the type of browser and operating system you use to access the Site, the date and time you access the Site, the pages you visit, and the addresses of pages from where you followed a link to the Site. We may use such information to analyze trends, administer the Site, track user’s movement around the Site, and gather demographic information. Such information is not linked to any information that is Personal Information, with the exception of the IP address which might be used to identify spamming attempts.

UVdesk also uses web analytics services, which currently include Google Analytics.  
Google Analytics is a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses cookies and similar technologies to analyse how users use the Site. The information generated about Site usage (including your shortened IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is used to evaluate visitors’ use of the Site, compile statistical reports on Site activity, and provide other services related to the Site and internet use. Google may also collect information about Site visitors’ use of other websites.

## List Of Cookies

List of cookie used by the Services

Cookie Name | Purpose | Websites Using the Cookie  
---|---|---  
UVSESSID | Used by UVdesk for maintaining the user session. | UVdesk  
MEMBERS | Used by UVdesk for maintaining the user session. | UVdesk  
uv-sidebar-status | Used by UVdesk internally for optimal functionality of site. | UVdesk  
uv-asideView | Used by UVdesk internally for optimal functionality of site. | UVdesk  
uv_form | Used by UVdesk internally for optimal functionality of site. | UVdesk  
qtrans_front_language | Used by UVdesk to indicate what language needs to be used on the website. | UVdesk  
  
## PUBLICLY AVAILABLE INFORMATION

Any information, video, image, data, text, documents, or other content posted at your direction onto a public area of the Site, such as Webkul Software Private Limited Blog / Demo , becomes publicly published content and will be available to all users of that public area of the Site, even if such content contains Personal Information. Please note that if you publish your contact information, you may receive unsolicited messages from users and visitors to the Site. We encourage you to publish only information you are sure you want to be accessible to anyone.

## THE WAY WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION

If you submit Personal Information to us through the Site:

We will use your Personal Information to improve our services to you, to contact you and to identify and authenticate your access to the Site’s services that you are authorized to access.

We may also use your email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding our services.

We may disclose your Personal Information or any information you submitted via the Site and its services if we have a good faith belief that disclosure of such information is helpful or reasonably necessary to (i) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (ii) enforce our Terms of Service including investigations of potential violations thereof, (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud or security issues, or (iv) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Webkul Software Private Limited, its users, yourself or the public.

## THE WAY WE USE ANONYMOUS INFORMATION

We may use Anonymous Information (as defined below), or disclose it to third party service providers, to improve our services and enhance your experience with the Site and its services. “Anonymous Information” means information which does not enable identification of an individual user, such as aggregated information about the use of our Site and services.

## CHOICE

You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to Webkul Software Private Limited. The notices we will provide where Webkul Software Private Limited collects Personal Information on the Site should help you to make this choice. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you can still visit many parts of the Site, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you.

## COLLECTION OF INFORMATION BY THIRD-PARTY SITES

Our Site may use a reputable third party to present or serve advertisements that you may see at our Site. These third party ad servers may use cookies, web beacons, clear gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements’ effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our Privacy Policy.

## INFORMATION SHARING

We may reveal information about visitors to the Site, customers and other third parties to better describe our services and usage by the visitors, however, these data will not reveal any personally identifiable information about the users.

We may disclose your personal information under lawful government requests if we believe that such action is necessary to prevent fraud or cyber crime to operate our systems properly or to protect the website, or the rights, property or personal safety of UVdesk or any person.  
We may provide links to third-party websites as part of the services we provide on this site. UVdesk is not responsible for the content of external websites, or for their privacy policies.

We reserve the right to transfer information (including your personal data) to a third party in the event of a sale, merger, liquidation, receivership or transfer of all or substantially all of the assets of UVdesk or any of its subsidiaries provided that the third party agrees to adhere to similar terms to this privacy policy.

## PAYMENT PROCESSING

Payments made on the Site are made through our payment gateway provider, PayPal. You will be providing credit or debit card information directly to PayPal which operates a secure server to process payment details, encrypting your credit/debit card information and authorising payment. Information which you supply to PayPal is not within our control and is subject to PayPal’s own privacy policy and terms and conditions.

## DATA RIGHTS

If you are located in countries that fall under the scope of the European General Data Protection Regulation, data protection laws give you rights with respect to your personal data which includes:

  * Request access to your personal data;

  * Request correction or deletion of your personal data;

  * Object to our use and processing of your personal data;

  * Request that we limit our use and processing of your personal data; and

  * Request portability of your personal data.

You can usually access, correct, or delete your personal data using your account settings and tools that we offer, but if you aren’t able to do that, you can reach us at support@uvdesk.com with your request.

EU individuals also have the right to make a complaint to a government supervisory authority.

## HOW LONG WE KEEP INFORMATION

We generally remove any kind of secure information like FTP or admin credentials of your e-commerce website that you share on the ticket when we no longer need it for the purpose that we have collected.

However, keeping information like web server logs that record information about a visitor to one of the websites, such as the visitor’s IP address, browser type, billing address and operating system, are kept within the system for approximately 90 days. We retain the logs for this period of time in order to analyze the traffic of websites and investigate issues if something goes wrong on one of our websites.

## LINKS TO OTHER SITES

Our Site contains links to other sites. Other sites may also reference or link to our Site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites.

## CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

The Site is not intended for or structured to attract children under the age of 18. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 18 years of age.

## SECURITY

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Notwithstanding anything contained in this Policy or elsewhere, Webkul Software Private Limited shall not be held responsible for any loss, damage or misuse of the User Information, if such loss, damage or misuse is attributable to a Force Majeure Event. A “Force Majeure Event” means any event that is beyond the reasonable control of Webkul Software Private Limited and includes, without limitation, fire, flood, explosion, acts of God, civil commotion, strikes, lock outs or industrial action of any kind, riots, insurrection, war, acts of government, power failure, sabotage, computer hacking, unauthorised access to computer data and storage device, system failure, virus, attacks, bugs, computer crashes, breach of security and encryption.

## CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

## QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at [support@uvdesk.in](mailto:support@uvdesk.in)

## GOVERNING LAW AND JURISDICTION

The terms and conditions of this Policy shall be governed by Indian Laws, and the courts in DELHI, shall only have exclusive jurisdiction to resolve/ adjudicate upon any disputes.
